<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Camelia Brennan</title>
    <link>/posts/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Camelia Brennan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Empress Of: Me</title>
      <link>/posts/blog/empress_of/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blog/empress_of/</guid>
      <description>The first time I saw Empress Of was in the summer of 2016, at Pitchfork Music Festival. It was one of those perfect festival shows where you’re packed into an insanely crowded space, but inebriated enough to not be annoyed by it, and simultaneously blown away by a breathtaking performance. Lorely Rodriguez commanded the room with her infectious electro pop music. Her signature hair twirled back and forth, as she danced with her head down — busy, attentive — while the entire room danced in unison, hypnotized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Q and Not U: Different Damages</title>
      <link>/posts/blog/q_and_not_u/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blog/q_and_not_u/</guid>
      <description>I sincerely think I may have listened to Q and Not U’s sophomore album Different Damage more times than any other album. It is a complete joy, and my first introduction to everyone’s favorite D.C. punk label, Dischord Records.
Following their debut album, No Kill No Beep Beep, Different Damage appeals more to your pop sensibilities, and feels slightly more disciplined and cohesive. The album combines sharp guitar riffs and crisp loud drums to fill your post-hardcore needs, while still being extremely danceable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mars Volt: Deloused In The Comatorium</title>
      <link>/posts/blog/the_mars_volta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blog/the_mars_volta/</guid>
      <description>I talk about this probably too much, but De-Loused in the Comatorium by The Mars Volta is a very good album.
As a huge fan of At The Drive In, the future seemed very uncertain after their breakup in 2001. In 2003, I didn’t even know The Mars Volta existed until someone popped this CD into my car stereo. This was the first concept album I ever heard, as well as my first introduction to progressive rock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alkaline Trio: s/t</title>
      <link>/posts/blog/alkaline_trio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blog/alkaline_trio/</guid>
      <description>In 2000 Asian Man Records released Alkaline Trio’s self titled album, which is a compilation of two EPs and a single. It was always my favorite Alkaline Trio release — though Maybe I’ll Catch Fire and Goddamnit! are incredibly close runner ups.
I was first introduced to the wide world of Napster in 6th grade, which was a real game changer. I initially downloaded some Alkaline Trio songs after the boy I had a debilitating crush on recommended them to me over AIM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Velvet Teen: Elysium</title>
      <link>/posts/blog/the_velvet_teen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blog/the_velvet_teen/</guid>
      <description>For the life of me, I cannot remember the name of a website I frequented in high school in the early 2000s, from a shared family computer in my mothers office. You could enter a band name, and it built out recommendations in a bubble map. As an adolescent girl, in addition to having a crush on every boy, I was also fixated with the entire Virginia post-hardcore scene. It almost goes without saying, but I was REALLY into Engine Down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NST Cophie: Mon’Da Center</title>
      <link>/posts/blog/nst_cophie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blog/nst_cophie/</guid>
      <description>I heard this album for the first time earlier this year, though it was originally released in the early 80’s.
While bunkering down in Brooklyn during a seemingly never ending pandemic induced societal collapse, Mon&amp;rsquo;Da Center was a bright glimmer of hope when everything else was falling apart. It is impossible to listen to NST Cophie’s afro-disco masterpiece, filled with back to back bangers, and not feel happier afterward — or at the very least, bop around a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wye Oak: The Knot</title>
      <link>/posts/blog/wye_oak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blog/wye_oak/</guid>
      <description>The first time I heard The Knot by Wye Oak I was interning at Merge Records after graduating college. It was 2009, and a very strange time to graduate. Job prospects were scarce, my boyfriend sucked, I was living at home, but being able to spend time with music I cared about made the future feel more optimistic.
That same year Merge was celebrating their 20 year anniversary with a festival, as they do every 5 years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
